Luke 8:17 everything that is concealed
will be brought to
light the things I try to keep
out all of these
years just found their way in Angels and
Demons on their Eternal war will destroy
us all
unattended John
Constantine you are a disgrace to our
kind we have plans for you
traitor enjoy the
Shadows it is only by the operations of
this Council that another War does not
begin but it shall begin
[Music]
now they are after metahumans in this
universe looking for the most powerful
ones to possess and take
over he's dead he's dead she's dead let
somebody knows
something this is a prophecy I thought
would never
happen end of the road this is your last
case John Your Last Day Out of
[Music]
Hell